

PERSONAL DATA:

- wicbelova.com
- Wroclaw, Poland
- @ vacova1988@gmail.com
- **(** +48 452 398 093









SKILLS:

- excellent work organization
- scrupulity and responsibility
- communication skills
- ability to work in a team
- knowledge of MS Office

LANGUAGE SKILLS:

- Polish language: level B1
- Russian language: native
- English language: level A2/B1

Victoria Belova

Accountant

I am an independent accountant with 5 years of experience in Belarusian accounting and 8 years experience in the field of taxes. I have been living in Poland since 2022 and studying Polish legislation (accounting and tax accounting). I am interested in developing as an independent accountant and then as a chief accountant in Poland. I am interested in tax law - I follow and read interpretations of regulations on an ongoing basis. I am also interested in continuous development of my skills and competences, which is why I take part in professional development, courses and training.

EXPERIENCE

2017-2021, 2023-2024

PhotoCeramics company, Belarus Accountant

- processing of accounting documents
- registering economic events on accounting accounts
- analysis and verification of entries in accounting accounts
- making payments, maintaining the organization's current accounts, controlling receivables and liabilities
- keeping records of accounting costs, reconciling them with general ledger accounts
- settlement of costs, including for tax purposes
- preparation of financial statements (balance sheet, profit and loss account)
- tax calculation (tax under the simplified tax system; VAT, corporate income tax, personal income tax)
- preparing and submitting tax returns

2009-2017, 2021-2022

Tax office, department of control over legal entities, Belarus
Tax inspector

• checking organizations compliance with tax and accounting regulations

- control of the completeness of reflection of the organization's revenues in accounting and tax reports
- verifying the legality of including the organization's expenses as costs included for tax purposes
- checking the correctness of tax settlements by organizations (VAT, personal and corporate income tax, land tax, real estate tax)

ADDITIONAL COURSES

2023-2024

Association of Accountants of Poland

speciality: accounting

2021-2022

The Rolling Scopes School

speciality: JavaScript/Front-end

2013

Association of Accountants of Belarus

speciality: accounting







EDUCATION

2004-2009

Francisk Skorina Gomel State University

speciality: economics

INTERESTS

Gym, reading, healthy lifestyle, development of personal and professional qualities

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruiting for the position I am applying for.